<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="StartApp">200148963</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_description">Navigate home</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_up_description">Navigate up</string>
    <string name="abc_action_menu_overflow_description">More options</string>
    <string name="abc_action_mode_done">Done</string>
    <string name="abc_activity_chooser_view_see_all">See all</string>
    <string name="abc_activitychooserview_choose_application">Choose an app</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_off">OFF</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_on">ON</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_alt_shortcut_label">Alt+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_ctrl_shortcut_label">Ctrl+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_delete_shortcut_label">delete</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_enter_shortcut_label">enter</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_function_shortcut_label">Function+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_meta_shortcut_label">Meta+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_shift_shortcut_label">Shift+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_space_shortcut_label">space</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_sym_shortcut_label">Sym+</string>
    <string name="abc_prepend_shortcut_label">Menu+</string>
    <string name="abc_search_hint">Search…</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_clear">Clear query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_query">Search query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_search">Search</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_submit">Submit query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_voice">Voice search</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with">Share with</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with_application">Share with %s</string>
    <string name="abc_toolbar_collapse_description">Collapse</string>
    <string name="app_name">Guide</string>
    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior">com.google.android.material.appbar.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>
    <string name="armas1">This is Free Fire\'s most recent assault rifle. It behaves like a kind of M4A1 but with worse features, except for damage. It\'s a good choice if you opt for medium distance combat, as you\'ll be able to do good damage. Keep in mind that you can add all kinds of extras except silencers, so it will always be a noisy weapon in your hands.</string>
    <string name="armas10">If you think you\'re going to spend more time inside buildings or in other enclosed spaces, SCAR is a good choice.</string>
    <string name="armas11">The mix of damage and shooting cadence, along with its long range and decent accuracy, make GROZA one of the best assault rifles in Free Fire. If it\'s already very good, the fact that we can add extras of all kinds makes your enemies tremble with fear. The downside is that it\'s only available in drops, i.e. in supply boxes.</string>
    <string name="armas12">Pay attention to these boxes because if you see one containing the GROZA weapon, take it immediately. You won\'t regret it!</string>
    <string name="armas13">The FAMAS is one of the best assault rifles in this Battle Royale, but also the hardest to handle. Bullets are always fired in bursts, so it\'s crucial to aim well so you don\'t waste them. It has a long range, plus decent damage and precision, making this the most lethal weapon in a short distance.</string>
    <string name="armas14">We recommend the FAMAS for those who are more experienced and know how to handle their recoil due to gusts.</string>
    <string name="armas2">Use the AN94 if you can\'t find a more powerful assault rifle.</string>
    <string name="armas3">The M4A1 is one of the most famous weapons in the game and the most powerful assault rifle. Add to that its good damage and precision, and it\'s no wonder that this weapon is the favorite of many players. In addition, it\'s often easy to find during a game, especially in military locations.</string>
    <string name="armas4">Its great advantage is that we can add all kinds of extras, and it is perfect for both novices and experienced players.</string>
    <string name="armas5">Armed with the highest damage and precision of any assault rifle, the M14 is a lethal weapon in the hands of skilled players. In range, it\'s only one point behind the M4A1, so it\'s useful at long range. It is true that it has the lowest shooting cadence in the list, but it is possible to add all kinds of accessories to turn the weapon into a more powerful one.</string>
    <string name="armas6">It is a weapon aimed at experienced players, and has a smaller magazine compared to the rest.</string>
    <string name="armas7">The AK is another of the best-known weapons not only in this game, but in the world of Battle Royales and shooters. The features do justice to its fame, as it is one of the rifles that have more damage and range. The negative point is that it is the least accurate of the list although, luckily, it can be solved with extras.</string>
    <string name="armas8">If you\'re patient with shots, two or three bullet bursts, you can eliminate enemies quickly.</string>
    <string name="armas9">SCAR isn\'t the most accurate weapon in the game either, and in fact, it\'s worse than AN94 in almost every feature. Its plus point is that it\'s the assault rifle that fires the most bullets per second, so it\'s useful in close-range matches. Fortunately, all possible accessories can be added to make up for these shortfalls.</string>
    <string name="bottom_sheet_behavior">com.google.android.material.bottomsheet.BottomSheetBehavior</string>
    <string name="character_counter_content_description">Character limit exceeded %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="character_counter_pattern">%1$d / %2$d</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_device_auth_instructions">Visit &lt;b&gt;facebook.com/device&lt;/b&gt; and enter the code shown above.</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_image_download_unknown_error">Unexpected error while downloading an image.</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_internet_permission_error_message">WebView login requires INTERNET permission</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_internet_permission_error_title">AndroidManifest Error</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_like_button_liked">Liked</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_like_button_not_liked">Like</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_loginview_cancel_action">Cancel</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_loginview_log_in_button">Log in</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_loginview_log_in_button_continue">Continue with Facebook</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_loginview_log_in_button_long">Log in with Facebook</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_loginview_log_out_action">Log out</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_loginview_log_out_button">Log out</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_loginview_logged_in_as">Logged in as: %1$s</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_loginview_logged_in_using_facebook">Logged in using Facebook</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_send_button_text">Send</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_share_button_text">Share</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_smart_device_instructions">To connect your account, open the Facebook app on your mobile device and check for notifications.</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_smart_device_instructions_or">- OR -</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_smart_login_confirmation_cancel">Not you?</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_smart_login_confirmation_continue_as">Continue as %1$s</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_smart_login_confirmation_title">Confirm Login</string>
    <string name="com_facebook_tooltip_default">You\'re in control - choose what info you want to share with apps.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unknown_issue">%1$s is having trouble with Google Play services. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="diam1">Become the best with these tips</string>
    <string name="diam10">It\'s not very smart to explore these areas from the beginning, but if we\'re halfway through the game, there will always be things to take. Surely there will be fewer players lurking around to eliminate us.</string>
    <string name="diam11">In places like this, it\'s also common to find kits to improve bulletproof vests. Pay attention as you explore because, although it\'s okay to have a level one vest, it\'s highly recommended to upgrade it soon. The last players will always have a powerful weapon.</string>
    <string name="diam12">Pay attention to the safe area</string>
    <string name="diam13">The safe zone is described by a white circle, which we can see both on the map and in the mini-map. Inside this zone we will be safe, since, outside of it, the radioactive storm will take away our life with the passage of time.</string>
    <string name="diam14">If we pay attention to the safe area, we will often see players running for their lives to get away from the storm, before it\'s too late. Situations like this are a perfect opportunity to eliminate opponents.</string>
    <string name="diam15">Look at the mini-map</string>
    <string name="diam16">The mini-map is very important to avoid a whole series of threats to our survival.</string>
    <string name="diam17">If you hear gunshots close to you, look for the red triangles in the mini-map, as they will indicate the origin of the shots. This way you will know where there are enemies nearby. At other times, we\'ll hear explosions and vehicles driven by players. Both will be marked by yellow or red dots around the mini-map. That will tell us which direction the sound is coming from.</string>
    <string name="diam18">In addition to radiation, there are also danger zones. These zones are marked by red circles with the label Danger. After a few seconds, a bomber will destroy that place, so get away as soon as possible! UAV drones reveal the position of players within the yellow circle. Never expose yourself to others, but stay close to see where the revealed players are.</string>
    <string name="diam19">Take cover</string>
    <string name="diam2">In Free Fire we have many tools at our disposal to become the last survivor standing, but you must also know how to use them. Discover how to become the best Free Fire player with these tips.</string>
    <string name="diam20">All over the map there are buildings, walls, containers, stones, trees, etc. Use them as cover! The worst thing we can do in this game is be exposed. While you\'re on the move, try to protect yourself with the environment so that you don\'t fall out of the way in the face of observant players.</string>
    <string name="diam21">However, that means we have to move carefully. We\'ll never know if behind that wall, or that wall of the building, hides an opponent with a shotgun, ready to get us out of the game with two surprise shots.</string>
    <string name="diam22">Use vehicles with care</string>
    <string name="diam23">The vehicles are used to move quickly to other places, where there is quality loot, and also to pass over the absent-minded players that we find on the road.</string>
    <string name="diam24">If we make too much noise, the other players will be able to hear us. For that reason, use cars, vans and motorcycles carefully, so as not to reveal our position.</string>
    <string name="diam3">Choose the right landing site</string>
    <string name="diam4">Choosing the landing site is only the first step to victory. Although it may seem trivial, it\'s not; determining where you\'ll start will allow you to decide whether to start the game right or not. It\'s important to choose a place isolated from other players, near a city but not so close to it.</string>
    <string name="diam5">Therefore, the best option is to fall out of towns and cities, observe where others fall and then enter to explore. It is fundamental not to expose ourselves too much until we are properly equipped, especially when we move around places with loot in quantity and quality, where many times there will be players.</string>
    <string name="diam6">Get equipment</string>
    <string name="diam7">As soon as we land, the first thing we have to do is to find weapons, protection, first aid kits, among other things. At the beginning of the game, the best thing to do is to grab everything we can find, as we can always improve and change the equipment.</string>
    <string name="diam8">Explore military sites</string>
    <string name="diam9">If there are no enemies in sight, it\'s a good idea to explore sites like watchtowers, cargo containers, trenches or military tents. There are usually good loot in these kinds of places, both in weaponry and supplies.</string>
    <string name="fab_transformation_scrim_behavior">com.google.android.material.transformation.FabTransformationScrimBehavior</string>
    <string name="fab_transformation_sheet_behavior">com.google.android.material.transformation.FabTransformationSheetBehavior</string>
    <string name="facebook_native_ads_id">181999142905459_182000052905368</string>
    <string name="facebook_native_custom">181999142905459_258539008584805</string>
    <string name="fb_banner">181999142905459_182000489571991</string>
    <string name="fb_fullscreen">181999142905459_182000359572004</string>
    <string name="fb_native_banner_ad_id">181999142905459_182000246238682</string>
    <string name="fbaddtestdevice">9777ac13-0042-4349-99a1-1487c10d6908</string>
    <string name="good_ap_id">ca-app-pub-4948109105438662~9731518545</string>
    <string name="google_banner_ad">ca-app-pub-4948109105438662/2225397763</string>
    <string name="google_fullscreen_ads_id">ca-app-pub-4948109105438662/2514840673</string>
    <string name="google_native_ads_id">ca-app-pub-4948109105438662/8418436872</string>
    <string name="google_test_id">A81D389E92C898E26C02CE9788320648</string>
    <string name="hide_bottom_view_on_scroll_behavior">com.google.android.material.behavior.HideBottomViewOnScrollBehavior</string>
    <string name="messenger_send_button_text">Send</string>
    <string name="mtrl_chip_close_icon_content_description">Remove %1$s</string>
    <string name="password_toggle_content_description">Show password</string>
    <string name="path_password_eye">M12,4.5C7,4.5 2.73,7.61 1,12c1.73,4.39 6,7.5 11,7.5s9.27,-3.11 11,-7.5c-1.73,-4.39 -6,-7.5 -11,-7.5zM12,17c-2.76,0 -5,-2.24 -5,-5s2.24,-5 5,-5 5,2.24 5,5 -2.24,5 -5,5zM12,9c-1.66,0 -3,1.34 -3,3s1.34,3 3,3 3,-1.34 3,-3 -1.34,-3 -3,-3z</string>
    <string name="path_password_eye_mask_strike_through">M2,4.27 L19.73,22 L22.27,19.46 L4.54,1.73 L4.54,1 L23,1 L23,23 L1,23 L1,4.27 Z</string>
    <string name="path_password_eye_mask_visible">M2,4.27 L2,4.27 L4.54,1.73 L4.54,1.73 L4.54,1 L23,1 L23,23 L1,23 L1,4.27 Z</string>
    <string name="path_password_strike_through">M3.27,4.27 L19.74,20.74</string>
    <string name="per1">Special Ability: The less life he has, the more armor he will penetrate with his attacks.</string>
    <string name="per10">Special Ability: becomes a bush, with a recharge time of several minutes.</string>
    <string name="per11">Price: 499 diamonds.</string>
    <string name="per12">Wukong is like a human who looks like a monkey. Or a monkey that looks like a human. We don\'t know, because he is such a mysterious character that nobody knows his past or his age. This character is good for those who want to play with a more passive style, always hidden and ready to give a death scare to an enemy who passes in front. The shotgun is your best friend!</string>
    <string name="per13">Special Ability: The game begins with more life than the rest of the characters.</string>
    <string name="per14">Price: 499 diamonds.</string>
    <string name="per15">Antonio is an orphan who created his own street gang. He grew up as a gangster and in seven years managed to get rid of all his rivals. If anyone thinks of threatening his family, let him prepare himself: he will do everything possible to protect them, even if it puts his life at risk.</string>
    <string name="per16">This character is the best if we want to have the advantage in the first encounters. His increased initial life translates into more durability at the beginning of the game.</string>
    <string name="per17">Special Ability: bulletproof vests are more resistant, so playing with Andrew takes longer to break.</string>
    <string name="per18">Price: 1000 coins (Andrew is a free character if you log in from the main menu).</string>
    <string name="per19">Andrew is a former policeman who spent much of his life chasing criminals to jail. Thanks to his experience, he became an expert in survival and armed combat. In addition, Andrew is extremely resistant to injury.</string>
    <string name="per2">Price: 1999 diamonds (only in package for the moment).</string>
    <string name="per20">A useful character for those of us looking for a defensive rather than an aggressive style.</string>
    <string name="per21">Special Ability: Kelly\'s sprint is faster than normal, allowing us to reach enemies, catch the loot before others, or escape dangers</string>
    <string name="per22">Price: 2000 coins or 399 diamonds.</string>
    <string name="per23">Kelly\'s real name is Shimada Kiriko. She is a teenager, still a student. She is an elite athlete who doesn\'t stop training on the athletics track or at the academy, making her the fastest character in Free Fire.</string>
    <string name="per24">Playing as Kelly will be the best option if we want to get to sites before others, or have an advantage in any chase on foot.</string>
    <string name="per25">Special Ability: companions receive more life by being revived by Olivia.</string>
    <string name="per26">Price: 2000 coins or 399 diamonds.</string>
    <string name="per27">A nurse by profession, Olivia is a specialist in caring for others. She always says that helping people is what makes her happiest, whether they are friends or enemies, regardless of whether it is a danger to her.</string>
    <string name="per28">She is a good character for the Duo and Squad modes, as she is able to heal teammates quickly and efficiently. However, if we choose her for Solo mode, it will be like playing with Eve and Adam, because it doesn\'t give us any personal advantage.</string>
    <string name="per29">Special Ability: the damage received inside the radioactive zone is less with Ford than with other characters.</string>
    <string name="per3">Shimada Hayato comes from an old Samurai family. He has a deep sense of honor and proudly carries the blood of his family, with its traditions but also curses. He is willing to do anything to protect his greatest secret and, to do so, he uses the Katana, whoever his opponent is.</string>
    <string name="per30">Price: 2000 coins or 399 diamonds.</string>
    <string name="per31">Ford was a sailor. The harsh life of the oceans increased their resistance and will to survive. He is the most mysterious character, whose secrets he does not want to reveal.</string>
    <string name="per32">This man is a good choice if we want to land in the most extreme places of the map and explore with tranquility. It is also useful to hide in the radioactive zone, for a short time, and surprise our adversary with an ambush, but watch your health!</string>
    <string name="per33">Special Ability: Nikita has the ability to recharge sub-machine guns more quickly, a real advantage in a one-on-one situation.</string>
    <string name="per34">Price: 2500 coins or 499 diamonds.</string>
    <string name="per35">Nikita is the professional bodyguard of Carolyn, the daughter of the president of the Free Fire organization. She has learned to use different weapons since she was a child, becoming a champion in different competitions.</string>
    <string name="per36">This woman is useful for those of us who want to make the most of a submachine gun\'s shooting cadence and magazine, but watch your ammunition!</string>
    <string name="per37">Special Ability: All vehicles driven by Misha reach a higher speed and receive less damage.</string>
    <string name="per38">Price: 8000 coins or 499 diamonds.</string>
    <string name="per39">Misha is a racing specialist, a very brave girl who loves speed and loves to leave all opponents under a cloud of dust. For her there are no curves, only straight roads.</string>
    <string name="per4">This character is tremendously useful for lovers of duels. If you try to have weapons with large magazines, in a long exchange you will end up doing more damage than your opponent, even if you have the same weapon.</string>
    <string name="per40">She\'s a suitable character for those of us who use vehicles frequently and are speed lovers. Hold on!</string>
    <string name="per41">Special Skill: Maxim takes less time to heal or eat a mushroom to earn EP points.</string>
    <string name="per42">Price: 8000 coins or 499 diamonds.</string>
    <string name="per43">Maxim is a regular competitor in contests who eats more, plus a very funny and smiling gamer. He loves streaming while playing against players from all over the world. But don\'t be fooled: if you think that by being bigger than him you\'re going to beat him in a food contest, you\'re wrong.</string>
    <string name="per44">Maxim is the best for those of us who base our game on stockpiling supplies.</string>
    <string name="per45">Special Ability: Kla\'s punches cause the most damage throughout the game, which is essential for the first few minutes of each game.</string>
    <string name="per46">Price: 8000 coins or 499 diamonds.</string>
    <string name="per47">Kla is a lonely man and a very experienced Muay Thai wrestler. He disappeared for years until he wanted to reappear, although totally changed: he has decided to take revenge with his own hands.</string>
    <string name="per48">This man is the best for those of us who like to land in places full of players; however, beware of ending up surrounded by bullets!</string>
    <string name="per49">Special skill: to be able to carry more AR bullets, as not all of them will take up space in our inventory.</string>
    <string name="per5">Special Ability: For a few seconds, let your teammates see where the enemies you have shot are.</string>
    <string name="per50">Price: 8000 coins or 499 diamonds.</string>
    <string name="per51">Paloma is an arms dealer, as beautiful as she is deadly. Years ago she was a model woman that all girls idolized, until one day she wanted to become an expert in buying and selling weapons. If there is illegal business in one place, Paloma will be there to benefit in every possible way.</string>
    <string name="per52">For those of us who want to have an advantage in ammunition and last longer in shooting exchanges, there\'s no one better than Paloma.</string>
    <string name="per53">Special Ability: For each enemy eliminated, Miguel gets EP points, which the rest of the characters can only get by eating a mushroom.</string>
    <string name="per54">Price: 8000 coins or 499 diamonds.</string>
    <string name="per55">Miguel is a very lethal and highly trained Special Forces soldier. He, along with the comrades of his battalion, has managed to bring justice against terrorists with great efficiency, throughout his career... until one day everything went wrong.</string>
    <string name="per56">Those of us who like to play aggressively and hunt down many enemies, this is our character.</string>
    <string name="per57">Special ability: can move faster when carrying a shotgun in hand.</string>
    <string name="per58">Price: 499 diamonds.</string>
    <string name="per59">Caroline is a very, very rich girl and spends her life surrounded by fans and numerous bodyguards. She is very close to her father and brother, and loves to do cosplay.</string>
    <string name="per6">Price: 499 diamonds.</string>
    <string name="per60">This young woman, one of the last members in the ranks of Free Fire, will be our best ally if we opt for close combat and exploration of buildings.</string>
    <string name="per7">Moco is one of the best hackers, known as an Internet legend. She\'s skillful, very intelligent, and able to get information from anywhere without leaving a trace - a ghost of networks!</string>
    <string name="per8">If you like to play with others, this character helps a lot in the task of ambushing enemies, thanks to the tag or identification of enemies with their ability.</string>
    <string name="s1">Save image</string>
    <string name="s2">Allow Ad to store image in Picture gallery?</string>
    <string name="s3">Accept</string>
    <string name="s4">Decline</string>
    <string name="s5">Create calendar event</string>
    <string name="s6">Allow Ad to create a calendar event?</string>
    <string name="s7">Test Ad</string>
    <string name="search_menu_title">Search</string>
    <string name="status_bar_notification_info_overflow">999+</string>
    <string name="tips1">Learn how to win gold and diamonds</string>
    <string name="tips10">Open free boxes and participate in Gold Royale</string>
    <string name="tips11">Every day we\'ll have a free box in the game store. To find this box, go to the Normal section and click on the Offer of the day section.</string>
    <string name="tips12">There is also the famous Luck Royale, which we can access from the main menu. There we test our luck. However, you can participate in Gold Royale with so-called normal vouchers or by spending gold. If we only use normal vouchers for Gold Royale, the first two rewards for weekly spins usually contain 100 gold coins each. To purchase these rewards, click on the red colored bags to the right of Gold Royale.</string>
    <string name="tips13">Finally, you\'ll sometimes get Lucky Draw, which is just an extra prize the game awards at random.  Press one of the three cards and you\'ll get another reward with minimal effort.  It usually gives little gold, and it\'s also possible to get memory fragments, among other items. </string>
    <string name="tips14">Receber prêmios sazonais</string>
    <string name="tips15">Todos nós gostamos de ser recompensados pelos nossos esforços! Ao jogar e se qualificar para o modo de classificação Free Fire, você receberá recompensas no final de cada temporada. Só por fazer parte dos qualificadores você receberá 1000 de ouro, mas se você jogar mais e subir na liga, os prêmios serão muito mais suculentos.</string>
    <string name="tips16">Comprar diamantes</string>
    <string name="tips17">Ninguém gosta de ter que gastar dinheiro, mas, exceto para Fire Pass, esta é a única outra maneira de conseguir diamantes. Se você usar qualquer outro método ilegal você será banido do Free Fire para sempre.</string>
    <string name="tips18">It is best to get a weekly or monthly membership, as you will receive more diamonds in total for less money. However, you must claim them daily. You can also take advantage of weekly offers because, besides buying diamonds, you will also get special vouchers to redeem for diamond boxes.</string>
    <string name="tips2">In Free Fire you don\'t just want to win, you want to show off unique weapon skins and features. To do this, you need to accumulate gold and diamonds by playing or paying with real money. Due to the amount of options, events and menus, many of us may feel confused.</string>
    <string name="tips3">Discover the methods of winning gold and diamonds, and how to spend them to unlock various items in the game. We have compiled the 5 ways to win gold and diamonds, supported by images to help you in the best possible way.</string>
    <string name="tips4">Play games</string>
    <string name="tips5">We will get a sum of gold just for participating, so entering a game will always be a good time invested. If you want to earn more money, it\'s good to practice and work hard, as the game rewards survival time, final position, eliminations and headshots. In addition, by playing games you will be able to complete daily challenges.</string>
    <string name="tips6">There are a variety of different challenges, especially if you have purchased Elite Pass (only unlocked with real money). When you complete a challenge, you\'ll receive one or more explosive medals. The tasks are usually to play a certain number of minutes, use specific weapons, reach a specific number of eliminations or end up in high positions.</string>
    <string name="tips7">Explosive medals are used for the Fire Pass. On this site, you\'ll unlock items as you get more medals. If you purchase Elite Pass, you\'ll get better rewards in the form of gold, diamonds and even skins. Otherwise, you can limit yourself to the Free Pass, but the rewards will be much scarcer.</string>
    <string name="tips8">Enter the game every day</string>
    <string name="tips9">This is a simple and safe way to earn gold, but in no case will we get diamonds just for entering. The daily rewards always come out when you enter the game and, as a general rule, you will get 350 gold each week. It\'s a very easy way to accumulate this virtual money, so try to get into Free Fire every day.</string>
    <string name="veh1">SPORTS CAR</string>
    <string name="veh10">AMPHIBIAN</string>
    <string name="veh11">If you see this vehicle and you need to cross a river, don\'t even think about it: use this amphibian. Driven by the water, this four-wheeled bike gives you total movement versatility across both Free Fire maps.</string>
    <string name="veh12">As you might expect, it\'s often found near areas where there\'s a river nearby. If you want to explore on a small island or something like that, do it without fear, as you can return to the main terrain without being exposed on the connecting bridges. Many are clever and wait on the other side of the bridge!</string>
    <string name="veh13">Also, as there is room for two people... the best vehicle to move freely in Duo mode!</string>
    <string name="veh14">MILITARY JEEP</string>
    <string name="veh15">This military jeep is one of the most abundant vehicles on Free Fire maps, but it\'s not very fast precisely. If you\'re driving up a steep hill, you\'ll notice that the jeep has a hard time overcoming the incline and, in fact, it\'s common for you to end up going downhill.</string>
    <string name="veh16">Drive this vehicle if there is no other option. It\'s true that the jeep can withstand a lot of shooting, especially if you turn your back on the shooters. The back of the jeep can get you out of more than one predicament!</string>
    <string name="veh17">The Tuk Tuk is a slow vehicle, weak and abundant in which areas. Never use it, unless you want to move quickly within the same village. Because it\'s a bit narrow, you can get between houses, so even if it sounds ridiculous, it\'s useful in chases.</string>
    <string name="veh18">If you want to quickly plunder small villages like the Bimasakti Strip, going with the Tuk Tuk is a good option.</string>
    <string name="veh19">VAN</string>
    <string name="veh2">This car has a very clear advantage over the rest: it is the fastest vehicle in Free Fire. It\'s true that it can\'t withstand as many blows as others, but the top speed at which it reaches attracts all players who are speed lovers.</string>
    <string name="veh20">The vans are the other vehicle that is very abundant on maps. It has some resistance, moderate speed and gives decent protection to the driver. It\'s a good option for getting from town to town, if you don\'t need to go back to the safe area immediately.</string>
    <string name="veh3">Don\'t hesitate to drive one of these cars as soon as you find one, especially if you\'re away from the safe zone. If you find this car, you\'ll be able to explore with peace of mind, knowing that in a matter of a minute you\'ll be halfway across the map.</string>
    <string name="veh4">Curious detail: as the sports car is very fast, if you hit a player who is on foot, he will fly away and will have extra damage from the fall.</string>
    <string name="veh5">The Monster Truck is the biggest and toughest vehicle. It\'s hard to destroy with gunshots and grenades, but the downside is that it\'s a bit slow. As it is immense, if you manage to reach an enemy with this vehicle, it is usual to eliminate it from a single charge.</string>
    <string name="veh6">One thing to keep in mind is that you\'ll almost certainly never find this 4x4 at the beginning of the game. As a general rule, Monster Truck will only appear at a few points on the map after being launched from an airplane. Watch out for the skies!</string>
    <string name="veh7">MOTORCYCLE</string>
    <string name="veh8">This motorcycle has a perfect combination of speed and handling, which is why many players prefer it to other vehicles. However, it has the disadvantage of exposing the rider, so if you don\'t go fast, you\'ll be an easy target to hit.</string>
    <string name="veh9">The good news is that, because the motorcycle is small, it allows you to move more quickly and pass narrow places without a lot of problems.</string>
</resources>
